# ANDY (AN) LIU

40 Summit Ave, • London, ON N6H 2G5 • (519) 697-4518 • andyvviiar@gmail.com

## **Highlights of Qualifications**

My one year of studying experience as a student (majored in front end developing) has honed my CSS3 and HTML5 skills, as well as my knowledge of responsive design and project management. I have the skills to create the perfect HTML, which makes it easy to find and fix any problems that arise later. Three years of experience in student council, getting involved in my school and faculty events with most students. Experience in entrepreneurial business and social media management when I create my own business.

#### Education

### Ontario College Diploma - Major: Interactive Media Design

Fanshawe College - London, ON

• CGPA: 3.70/4.30

Related Courses:

- Design & Image
- Digital Media Theory & Project Management
- Web development

- Multimedia Production
- Multimedia Authoring
- Motion Design

Master of Commerce - Major: MBA

Trinity Western University - Vancouver, BC

• Completed one semester study in management

Expected: Apr.2019

Sept,2016- Dec.2016

Completed: 2016

Bachelor of Engineering – Major: Software Engineering

School of Software, JiangXi Agriculture University – Nanchang, CHINA

• CGPA: 3.50/4.30

Related Courses:

- Web development technology (Java or .net)
- Visual modeling and UML
- Web development foundation

- Principles of computer composition and design of assembly language program
- JAVA program design
- Large database technology (oracle)
- Database principles and application

# **Work Experience**

**Startup CEO** – Farmhouse – NanChang, China

2014-2016

• Demonstrated professional and technical ability, management ability, social communication skills, innovation ability, and strong comprehensive ability.

**Teaching Assistant** – Global Education & Technology Co., Ltd. – NanChang, China Dce.2015-Apr.2016

- Demonstrated ability to coordinate with professors based on the course schedule
- Gained experience of marking students' assignments accurately with strong work ethic

Barista – Starbucks Coffee – NanChang, China

Oct.2012-Apr. 2013

- Demonstrated ability to work independently at a fast pace and under pressure when serving up to 100 customers per shift during peak hours
- Developed and displayed ability to communicate with customers considerately, accommodating their preferences and choices, especially in customizing beverages

## **Volunteering and Service**

Rt gulf gpv- Hcpuj cy g'Ej kpgug Uqekgy/- Napf qp, QP

Jan.2018- Present

- Vq"ugtxg"uwf gpvu"cpf "dtkpi "dgpghkuu"\q"vj go 0'Hqt"gzco r ng="ngv'uwf gpvu"i gv'\q"npqy "gcej "qvj gt" cpf "kpvgi tcvg"kpvq"Ecpcf kcp"nkhg"cu"uqqp"cu"r quukdng.
- To help students in our club to improve themselves, like social skills, confidence, etc.

Class Representer – The ESLi Student Council – Vancouver, BC

Sep.2016-Dec.2016

• Was responsible for communicating information regarding all activities as well as encouraging classmates to take advantage of other opportunities to get involved in the broader TWU campus.

**Kpvgt pcvkqpcnlXqnvpvggt** – *Ucpi Zk'Ci t kewnwt g'Wpkxgt uk* ( – P cpEj cpi , Ej kpc

Pqx. 2014

Vj g"5tf "Y qtrf "Eqphgtgpeg"qp"Nqy /ectdqp"Geqpqo { "cpf "vj g'9vj "Ej kpc"I tggp"Hqqf "Gzrq "

- Provided excellent service to guests in attendance and was responsible for helping to organize the guest reception ceremony.
- Was responsible for explaining the exhibition to guests (mainly in English, supplemented by Chinese) and protecting all exhibits and equipments.

College Student Union Office Director – JiangXi Agriculture University – NanChang, China

Sep.2014- May.2015

- Was responsible for coordinating all aspects of the work, as well as the day-to-day affairs of the student union.
- Establishing and improving the Institute of Students rules and regulations.
- Organized student meetings, and checked the implementation of the decision of the meeting.
- Promptly discovered and resolved internal problems and work contradictions.

### **Awards**

14WHH WS	
Top Ten Outstanding League Secretary Award – JiangXi Agriculture University	2012-2013
<ul> <li>Award for Organizing and coordinating class activities and discipline, and leadership skills</li> </ul>	
Science and Technology Academic, Innovation and Entreprenurship Scholarship  – JiangXi Agriculture University	2013-2014
The Second-class Scholarship – JiangXi Agriculture University	2014-2015
The Third-class Scholarship – JiangXi Agriculture University	2013-2014
The Third-class Scholarship – JiangXi Agriculture University	2012-2013
GzegngpvFgrw{ 'Fkt gevqt '- JiangXi Agriculture University	2013-2014